Guide to the Felipe Ehrenberg Papers, ca. 1964-2000
Department of Special Collections
- Series 12: Academic and Professional Institutions, Organizations, Groups, etc.
  - CEDART [Coordinacion General de Educacion Artistica] / INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Antecdentes y Proyecto Reestructuracion (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Garcia, Miguel - Expediente CEDART '80 [Coordinacion General de Educacion Artistica] (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord ENS / ART / Memorias Curso [?] '80 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Prom. Nal Expos 1 / Programas Exposiciones '80 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - SEP / DIR GRAL PROM CULT / Tuxtepec (ITA 3 / Casa) '80 {Secretaria de Educacion Publica / Direccion General de Promocion Cultural; Instituto Technologico Agropecuario)] (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord Ens. Artistica / Cuadernos de Apoyo (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Union Maestros / Casas de la Cultura (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord / Ed Art / Talleres Libres P.A.G. [Plan de Actividades Generadoras] (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord / Ed Art / Guias por Area/ P.A.G. [Plan de Actividades Generadoras] (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord / Ed / Art / Leon '81 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord Ensen. Art / Visitas Cedarts y Casas (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord Ens. Artistica / Matamoros '81 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord Ed Art / Toxtepec (Casa / ITA3 [Instituto Tecnologio Agropecuario #3]) '81 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Reunion / Prom / Cult / Ed / Artistica '81 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord / Ed Art / Reportes Varios (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord / Ens / Art / Varios (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] / Coord / Ed Art / Proposiciones y Desarollo (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Foro Arte Contemporaneo (INBA) [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - SEP / DIR / PROM / CULT / Viaje Nicaragua - '81 [Secretaria de Educacion Publica / Direccion / Promocion / Cultura] (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Instituto Regional de Belle Artes - Matamoros (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - [Coloquio: La generacion de ruptura; Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes (INBA) June 30 - July 1, 1997] (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Texto Inaugural IVEC - Dra Ida Pramolini [Instituto Veracruzano de la Cultura] (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Artes Plasticas: Varios (IVEC) [Instituto Veracruzano de la Cultura] (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - SEP - IVEC - Programas Cursos Varios [Secretaria de Educacion Publica - Instituto Veracruzano de la Cultura] (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - IVEC [Instituto Veracruzano de la Cultura] - Correspondencia Diversa (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Sylabus: Mural, Cartel, lab Editorial IVEC [Instituto Veracruzano de la Cultura] (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Artes Plasticas - Minutas - IVEC [Instituto Veracruzano de la Cultura] (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Censo Artistas / Formas / IVEC [Instituto Veracruzano de la Cultura] (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Artes Plasticas/ Prensa / Provisional - IVEC [Instituto Veracruzano de la Cultura] (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Diario Personal - Artes Plasticas - IVEC [Instituto Veracruzano de la Cultura] (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - UV [Universidad Veracruzana] - Edit. Esc. Artes Plasticas (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Instituto de Investigaciones Esteticas (U.V.) [Universidad Veracruzana] (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Autogobierno UNAM [Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico] (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Instituto de Investigaciones Esteticas / UNAM [Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico] (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - UAM - UNAM y Otros Instituciones [Universidad Autonoma Metropolitana - Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico] (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Seminario UNAM [Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico] - Problemas Esteticos de la Urbe] (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Instituto Potosino de Bellas Artes (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Asociacion Mexicana de Artes Plasticas, A.C. [AMAPAC] (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - PAVAC [Profesionales de la Artes Visuales A.C.] (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - SOMART (Sociedad Mexicana de Artes Plasticas) (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - C.R.E.C. [Centro Regional de Ejercicos Culturales] Xico (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - C.R.E.C. [Centro Regional de Ejercicos Culturales] = Xico a traves de los anos, Julio '76 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Consejo Nacional de las Artes (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Consejo Mex Foto Organo informativo (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - C.M.F. [Consejo Mexicano de Fotografia] Cursos y Talleres (Mimeo) (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Consejo Mexicano de Fotografia - Coloquios Primero (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Consejo Mexicano de Fotografia - Coloquio 2nd (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Consejo Mexicano de Fotografia - Tercer Coloquio LatinoAmericano de Fotografia (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Consejo Mexicano de Fotografia - Diversos Admon. (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Consejo Mexicano de Fotografia - Felipe Personales (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Consejo Mexicano de Fotografia - Recortes Diversos (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Consejo Mexicano de Fotografia - Info Diversa (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Fotografia - Primer Coloquio Nacional / Junio 1984 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Coalicion - Simposio Zacualpan (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Lenguajes Paralelos, Zacualpan Coalicion (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Cooperativa Chucho el Roto (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - I.C.O.M. [Internacional Council of Museums] 12 Congreso Mexicano (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Grupo Arte Aca (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Grupo R.A.C. [Realizadores de Arte y Cultura] (Veracruz) (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - AIR (Art Information Registry) (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - L.A.C.E. [Los Angeles County Exhibitions] (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - I.A.C. (International Artists Cooperative) (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - The Institute for Art and Urban resources / Clocktower (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Organizationes Varias (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - [Mailers from the Artists in Education Program, San Antonio, Texas - other similar material] (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - [University of New Mexico: Brochure for October 1995 exhibit] (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Programa Para El Desarrollo Integral de la Salud: Propuesto por: Centro Para EL Desarrollo Integral De La Salud ""Toltecayotl,"" A.C. (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Salon Independiente (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Salon Independiente (Recortes) (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Salon Independiente - Recortes sin clasif. (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Series 13: Social and Political Activism
  - [Correspondence re appeal to release Mexican political prisoners, circa 1970] (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Correspondencia contestada (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, etc. regarding Mexican poltical prisoners] [1 of 2] (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, etc. regarding Mexican poltical prisoners] [2 of 2] (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - [European Committee for the Defence of Mexican Political Prisoners (British Section): correspondence, etc.] (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - [Material concerning Mexican political prisoners; European Committee for the Defence of Mexican Political Prisoners] [1 of 3] (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - [Material concerning Mexican political prisoners; European Committee for the Defence of Mexican Political Prisoners] [2 of 3] (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - [Material concerning Mexican political prisoners; European Committee for the Defence of Mexican Political Prisoners] [3 of 3] (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - [Miscellaneous material regarding political repession in Latin America] (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - PSUM [Partido Socialista Unificado de Mexico] -- 36 / Comision de Organizacion (Ehrenberg) (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - PSUM [Partido Socialista Unificado de Mexico] -- 36 / Comision de Propaganda (Ehrenberg) (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - PSUM [Partido Socialista Unificado de Mexico] -- 36 / Comision de Finanzas (Ehrenberg) (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - PSUM [Partido Socialista Unificado de Mexico] -- 36 / Datos para Platforma Cultural Electoral - F.E. (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - PSUM [Partido Socialista Unificado de Mexico] -- 36 / Comision de Prensa y Publicidad (Ehrenberg) (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - PSUM [Partido Socialista Unificado de Mexico] Actas Electorales (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Subasta PSUM [Partido Socialista Unificado de Mexico] - 36 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Tepito (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Demandas y Peticiones (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - [Tepito material] [1 of 2] (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - [Tepito material] [2 of 2] (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - El Zaguan - Proyecto Antologia (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Correspondencia (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Centro Cultural Tepito (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Cooperativa: Modelo Acta Constitutiva (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Delagacion Cuauhtemoc / Subdeleg. Tepito (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Presidencia y D.D.F. (PRI) (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Particulares Proposiciones y Consideraciones Sobre el Sismo (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Centro de Enlace, Diaz de Leon [CEDL] I, Prensa (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Centro de Enlace, Diaz de Leon [CEDL] II, Prensa (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Centro de Enlace, Diaz de Leon [CEDL] III, Prensa (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Centro de Enlace, Diaz de Leon [CEDL] IV, Prensa (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Asociacion Civil / C. Enlace Diaz de Leon (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Papaleria Cnetro de Enlace (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - CEDL [Centro de Enlace Diaz de Leon]: Angel Duran y Redolfo Lozano (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - CEDL [Centro de Enlace Diaz de Leon] / Rocio Islas (Hija Jose Vega) (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - CEDL [Centro de Enlace Diaz de Leon] / Maria Esther Gonzalez de Flores / Diaz de Leon 20 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Casos Atenidos (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Obra Teatral L. Guilmain / FIRT [Fondo Independiente para la Reconstruccion de Tepito] (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Material / Folleto (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Donativos (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Prensa / Copias (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Donantes Extranjeros Corresp. (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Plantones, 9 - 14 Junio, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Domicilios Privados y Otros (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Diverso y Trivia (Revisor Posibles deltos para memoria) (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Renovacion y Sedue (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Sanchez, Maria Cornejo; Viuda de Sanchez (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Vallejo, Maria del Carmen (Carmela) CEDL [Centro de Enlace de Diaz Leon] (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Rodriguez Rodriguez, Maximino (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Silva, Raul Gonzalez (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - [Miscellaneous material concerning September 1985 earthquake and relief effort for the Tepito barrio of Mexico City] [1 ofd 3] (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - [Miscellaneous material concerning September 1985 earthquake and relief effort for the Tepito barrio of Mexico City] [2 ofd 3] (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - [Miscellaneous material concerning September 1985 earthquake and relief effort for the Tepito barrio of Mexico City] [3 ofd 3] (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - 1er Aniversario Sismo, 19 Sept., 1986 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Foros y Encuentros (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - [Miscellaneous material concerning earthquake in El Salvador] (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Programa Bario a Bario: Ayuda vecinal a damnificados de El Salvador (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Escrito Original - Barrio a Barrio (1+1) + copies (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Escrito Original - Barrio a Barrio (1+1) [photos] (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Bitacora El Salvador, Barrio a Barrio (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - B a B [Barrio a Barrio], Convenios y Relaciones con Fideicomiso (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - B a B [Barrio a Barrio]: Correspondencia Diversa (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - B a B [Barrio a Barrio] CREFAC [Centro de Reorientacios Familiar Comonitaria] (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - B a B [Barrio a Barrio]: Bitacora Dolores Campos (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - B a B [Barrio a Barrio]: ASTAC (Asociacion) (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Barrio a Barrio / Reuniones PM - Organiza Clones Vecinales (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Barrio a Barrio - Gastos (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Barrio a Barrio / Prensa Mexico (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - B a B [Barrio a Barrio]: Gral del San Salvador (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Barrio a Barrio / Prensa San Salvador (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Medalla Roque Dalton - 1987 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - UNTS y FENASTRAS [Unidad Nacional Trabajadores Salvadoreanos; and Federacion Nacional Sindical de Trabajadores Salvadorenos] (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Series 14: Early Editorial Work, and Publishing Material
  - Baspet, Savo '64 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    Two newspaper articles written by Ehrenberg, Mexico City Times, October 1964.
  - Lopez Miarnau, Rafael, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    Interview[?] with Lopez Miarnau, ts.
  - July, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    ""Art in Mexico"" section, Mexico City Times, Felipe Ehrenberg, editor.
  - August, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - September, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - October, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - November, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - December, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - January, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - August, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - September, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - October, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Montenegro (Box 92, Folder 19)
    Film ""gossip"" column, Mexico City Times[?], late 1964. Felipe Ehrenberg writing under the pseudonym ""Montenegro[?]
  - Libro Accion Libre - Propaganda (Box 92, Folder 20)
    Brief history and description of Beau Geste Press / Libro Accion Libre
  - Borgen - Forlag (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Casillas, Martin: Editores (Box 93, Folder 1)
    Editorial material, photographs, correspondence, etc. regarding collaboration with several authors for Martin Casillas Press.
  - Copies of Used Originals, July (Box 93, Folder 2)
    8 prints on artist's boards, cropping marks, annotations.
  - Twenty One: Art and Culture (20/1) (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Domes Editorial (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Television (Cuento, Canto y Color) (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Series 15: Personal Papers
  - Accidente (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Banco Mexicano del Golfo (Xalapa) (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Banco Nacional Mex (Banamex) (Coatepec) (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Chirimoya LA (Camioneta) (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - CCOC - Albaniles {Centro de Capacitation para Obreros de la Construccion] (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Cria Conejos (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Dibujos Jovencito (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Gasolinera - Crucero (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - SISA Publicidad {Servicio Industrial, S.A.] (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Sr. Felipe Ehrenberg [correspondence, other material from Nicho Ehrenberg and family] (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - SISA Publicidad {Servicio Industrial, S.A.] (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Series 16: Miscellaneous Photographs and Other Material
  - Artistas Varios y Anonimos (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Films, fotos - Cinema (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Fotos Eventuales (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Philippines (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Wednesday [photographs] (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - 4 - MCT Baspet Savo '64 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    Transparency
  - [Passport to Adventure: An Interactive Trip of Global Proportions. Stanton, Timothy; proposal and overview for computer game] (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Rini Templeton's Drawings (Box 94, Folder 10)
    Photocopies
  - Fotos Varias (Artistas) (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Series 17: Exhibition Announcements by Other Artists, Galleries, Institutions, or Museums
  - Exhibits by Artist: A (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Exhibits by Artist: B [1 0f 2] (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Exhibits by Artist: B [2 0f 2] (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits by Artist:C [1 0f 2] (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits by Artist: C [2 0f 2] (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits by Artist: D - F (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits by Artist: G [1 of 2] (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits by Artist: G [2 of 2] (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits by Artist: H -L [1 of 2] (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits by Artist: H -L [2 of 2] (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits by Artist: M [1 of 2] (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits by Artist: M [2 of 2] (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits by Artist: N -P [1 of 2] (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits by Artist: N -P [2 of 2] (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits by Artist: Q - R [1 of 2] (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits by Artist: Q - R [2 of 2] (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits by Artist: S - T [1 of 2] (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits by Artist: S - T [2 of 2] (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits by Artist: U - Z [1 of 2] (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits by Artist: U - Z [2 of 2] (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous artists: Exhibition announcements [1 of 5] (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous artists: Exhibition announcements [2 of 5] (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous artists: Exhibition announcements [3 of 5] (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous artists: Exhibition announcements [4 of 5] (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous artists: Exhibition announcements [5 of 5] (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Alta Moda Decoracion (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Carillo Gil (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Casa de la Cultura, Azcapotzalco (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - El Centro Cultural / Arte Contemporaneo y La Fundacion Cultural Television (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Centro Historico de la Ciudad de Mexico (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Casa del Lago; Casa de la Cultura de Juchitan, Oaxaca (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Departmento del Distrito Federal [DDF], Desarollo Socicultur (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Encuentro Nacional de Arte Joven (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Expoarte '95 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Galeria Arte Contemporaneo (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Galeria de Arte Mexicano (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Galeria Pecanins (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Galeria de Arte - Rafael Matos (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Galleries: miscellaneous [1 of 2] (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Galleries: miscellaneous [2 of 2] (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] [1 of 2] (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - INBA [Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes] [2 of 2] (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Instituto de Ciencias Sociales y Humanidades - BUAP [Benemerita Universidad Autónoma de Puebla] (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - ISSSTE Cultura [Insituto de Seguridad y Servicios Sociales de los Trabajadores de Estado] (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Loteria Nacional para la Asistencia Publica (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - MACAY [Museo de Arte Contemporaneo Ateneo de Yucatan] (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Mexican Fine Arts Center Museum, Chicago (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Museo de Aguascaliente (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Museo de Arte Moderno (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Museo Biblioteca Pape (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Museo - Taller Jose Clemente Orozco (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Primer Festival de la Juventud Mexicana 1983 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - SAIC [School of the Art Institute of Chicago] (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Los Talleres (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Tucson Museum of Art (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Universidad de las Americas - Puebla [UDLA] (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Universidad Autonoma Metropolitana [UAM] (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Museo Universitario Del Chopo (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Museo Universitario de Ciencias y Arte (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Universidad Iberoamericana (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - UNAM [Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico] (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - University of New Mexico (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Universidad Veracruzana (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - World Print Council (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous invitations, exhibit announcements, etc. (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Cicero Centenario (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Montevideo 1996 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Uribe, Juan Camilo (Box 105, Folder 12)